OLUMBA SOLOMON

UX/UI DESIGNER & FRONT END DEVELOPER

AGE

26 (31/03/1995)

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

HTML
CSS
JAVASCRIPT
REACT JS (IN PROGRESS)
ADOBE XD(DESIGN,
PROTOTYPING & TESTING)
ILLUSTRATOR
CLI
VERSION CONTROL (GIT)

PERSONAL SKILLS

Creative
Organized
Time proficient
A Team player
A Fast learner

CONTACT

+234 90 2699 7546 +234 90 8028 4052 olumbasolomon08@gmail.com Address: 14, Onaara Street, Ejigbo, Lagos. https://github.com/Solumba

NYSC CERTIFICTE NUMBER

A003506011

PROFILE

I am a self-taught front-end web developer looking forward to a successful career in web and software development. I am self-motivated and subjected to constantly develop my skills and grow professionally. Learning by myself, I experienced a lot of failures that left me with core personal values - patience and perseverance.

EXPERIENCE

TELEMARKETING

Outsource Global. | Apr 2019 - Nov 2020

Pitching the company's services to potential US based clients.
Working in teams to achieve company's targets and goals.

IT ADMIN / FRONT DESK OFFICER

Kefina Emerald Hotels| Feb 2017 - Dec 2018

Computer/software maintenance and installation.

Check in and Checkout Guest using hotel man software.

Posting of day to day guest payment history to the account office using hotel man.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE, MAJOR IN COMPUTER SCIENCE.

Tansian University | 2011 - 2015

UNDERGRADUATE EXPERIENCE

IT TRAINEE

Nigerian National Petroleum Corporation | Apr 2014 - Nov 2014

ITD Help Desk, Service Support: Effectively resolving major and minor problems as regards to computer hardware and software related issues.

Networks: as a team leader organizing members of my team and ideas and resources to solve network related issues on a steady among four different blocks.

Applications: working directly with Microsoft staff to make computations on NNPC Calabar tank using Microsoft Excel.

IT TRAINEE

Power Holding Company Of Nigeria | Mar 2014

Secretary, office of the AGM: accurate record keeping of the company's financial records and making mathematical computations using Microsoft excel and other Microsoft spreadsheet packages.

CAFE ADMIN

Tansian University Café | 2012 - 2014

Network Admin: organizing the café affairs, assigning students Wi-Fi passwords and tackling network and server related issues.

Organizing computer tutorials on the use of Microsoft excel and PowerPoint.

HOBBIES

Chess

Snooker

Music

Travel

International Politics.